[
	{
		"front" : "The term “whiskey” is actually derived from the Gaelic words 'uisage beatha', which in turn came from the Latin 'Acqua Vitae', meaning?",
		"back" : "Water of Life"
	},
	
	{
		"front" : "Which country has the oldest reference of producing whiskey?",
		"back" : "Ireland"
	},
	{
		"front" : "What is the minimum number of years whiskey needs to be distilled before it can be considered whiskey?",
		"back" : "3"
	},
	{
		"front" : "Which scotch brand was the first to sell single malt whiskey in airports?",
		"back" : "Glennfiddich"
	},
	{
		"front" : "How many bottles of scotch are exported every second?",
		"back" : "38"
	},
	{
		"front" : "If you order whiskey,'neat', what can you expect?",
		"back" : "No ice"
	},
	{
		"front" : "What does Jessica think some of the older whiskeys taste like?",
		"back" : "An old leather chair"
	},
	{
		"front" : "Scotch is just whiskey made in Scotland.  True or False?",
		"back" : "True"
	},
	{
		"front" : "All bourbon is whiskey.  True or False?",
		"back" : "True"
	},
	{
		"front" : "What type of whiskey is the product of a single distillery?",
		"back" : "Single malt"
	}
]